你认为我们这次的猎杀目标是什么
What do you think it is that we're hunting?
动物  植物也或是矿物质东西
Animal, vegetable, mineral.
我知道在你们眼里我是个老废物了
I know you boys think I'm a bag of loose screws.
马丁救了老爸的次数我们数都数不过来
Martin saved dad's ass more times than we can count.
他是个了不起的猎人
He's a great hunter.
不  我不是  我很没用
No, I'm not. I'm useless.
你问我是不是失去了谁
You asked me if I lost someone.
没错  我的丈夫
I did -- my husband.
艾米利亚与唐白头偕老
艾米利亚  你还好吗
Amelia, you okay?
是唐
It's Don.
他还活着
He's alive.
我叫本尼
I'm Benny.
我或许就会是
I just might be that hunter
那个碰到本尼还结果了他的猎魔人
that runs into Benny one day and ices him.
我想这事是车到山前必有路  对吗
I guess we'll cross that bridge when we come to it, won't we?
对
Yeah.
你总是这句话
Yeah. You keep saying that.
如 今
古德瑞的法式餐厅
路易斯安那州 卡伦科
我送安东尼回家  所以厨房交给你了
I sent Anthony home, so the kitchen's all yours.
一定要锁好门  设好报警器
And be sure to lock up the door and set the alarm,
关掉空调  检查火炉  检查浅锅
turn off the a/c, check the burners, check the griddle...
还有收拾冷盘食物
And clear off the cold table.
我知道了  快走吧
I got it. Go on, now.
谢谢你  罗伊
Thank you, Roy.
还有别忘了算清收支  登记入账
Oh, and don't forget to "Z" out the register...
批处理好POS机
And batch out the credit-card machines.
我知道
I know.
亲爱的  我又不是第一次做了  好吗
Darlin', it's not my first rodeo, all right?
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
那个伊丽莎白  真是个好女孩
Hell of a girl, that Elizabeth.
是啊
Yeah.
是啊  真是好女孩
Yeah, she really is.
-再续一杯  -好
- Refill? - Sure.
有计划追她吗
You got designs?
没
Nah.
对于我来说  她更像是个小妹妹
She's more like a little sister to me, you know?
那你不介意我试一试吧
So you don't mind if I take a shot?
尽可一试  首长
She's all yours, chief.
续杯
Please?
谢谢
Thanks.
尖牙
对
Yeah.
你确定吗
And you're certain?
确定吗
You sure?
那好  你先跟紧  等我消息
Okay. Great. Just, uh, just hang tight till you hear from me, okay?
是谁
Who is it?
不  听着  我让你跟紧就好
No, listen to me. I said hang tight.
我们得走了
We got to get.
能让我先吃完汉堡吗
Can I at least finish my burger?
有人被吸血鬼杀死了  迪恩
We got a vamp kill, Dean --
在路易斯安那州的卡伦科
Carencro, Louisiana.
好久没都吃过蔬菜海鲜辣炖汤了
It's been a while since I've had some étouffée.
谁提供的线索
Who's the source?
马丁・奎恩
Martin Creaser.
抱歉  刚刚有那么一瞬
Sorry -- for a minute there,
我以为你说的是马丁・奎恩
I thought you said Martin Creaser.
疯人院的疯狂马丁
Crazy Martin from the loony bin?
上个月他在格伦代尔泉医院获释了
Glendale Springs discharged him last month.
然后呢
And?
难道他不应该在保护病房拼玩具玩吗
Shouldn't he be assembling toys in a padded room?
他怎么又重操旧业了
What's he doing back on the job?
我请他这么做的
I asked him.
你什么
You what?
他出来的时候给我打了电话
Look, he called me when he got out, okay,
问我有没有办法
asked if I had anything for him
帮助他重新开始猎魔
that might help him ease back into the game.
他似乎康复了  基本康复了
He seemed okay -- mostly --
所以我答应帮他
so I said yes.
这几周我都让他盯着本尼
I've had him tracking Benny for the past week.
你让"基本康复"的马丁去盯着本尼
You put "mostly okay" Martin on Benny?
"基本康复"的人猎魔都做些啥
What is "mostly okay" doing hunting at all?
不是猎魔  迪恩  是跟踪
Not hunting, Dean -- tracking.
只是观察报告  我交代得十分清楚
Observe and report only. I was crystal clear about that.
真不敢相信
Wow. I can't believe that.
是吗  迪恩  你不敢相信
Really, Dean? You don't believe that?
因为本尼是个吸血鬼
Because Benny's a vampire.
而一个称职的猎人
And any hunter worth his salt
不该让吸血鬼在外自由游荡
isn't gonna let one just walk around freely.
所以我让马丁监视他
So I had Martin keep tabs on him.
现在看来我的决定是正确的
And right now, it's looking like I made the right call.
马丁说这事是本尼做的
So Martin's saying Benny did this?
对
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
"好吧"
"Okay"?
如果本尼在路易斯安那吸干人血
If Benny's in Louisiana draining folks...
我们该去查查看
we should look into it.
欢迎来到路易斯安那
日租房
你说在找"火山爆发"[也可译作长牙]
You said "look for an eruption."
看看维苏威火山
How's Mount Vesuvius?
我大概一周前到的镇上
I got into town about a week ago.
昨晚之前一无所获  他没有行动
Up until last night, nothing. He's been clean.
他在干什么
Doing what?
干他自己的活儿
Just minding his own business.
在小酒馆里打工
Working at the gumbo shack.
本尼在小酒馆里打工
Benny's working at the gumbo shack?
对  端盘子  倒咖啡  什么活都干
Yeah. Slinging hash, pouring coffee -- the whole bit.
在你面前他可能叫本尼
And he may be Benny to you.
但是这里的人叫他罗伊
Folks around here call him Roy.
马丁  你确定自己没事吗
Martin, you sure you're running on a full charge?
没事
Y-yeah.
早上用一下休克疗法
L-little s-shock therapy in the morning,
我就活蹦乱跳了
and I-I'm good to go.
说说昨晚发生什么事
Tell us what happened last night.
我像往常一样跟踪他回家
So, I followed him home, just like every night.
他拐上一条小路
He turned up a path.
我听到一声尖叫
I hear a scream.
跟过去一看
I catch up.
一具尸体
Boom -- there he is.
酒馆里罗伊打量的那个傻瓜  被吸干了
The old coot that Roy was eyeballing at the joint -- vamped.
等等...你到底有没有亲眼看到本尼杀人
Wait -- did you actually see Benny kill the guy or not?
我看到的够多了
I saw enough.
如果你没亲眼看到他动手
Well, then, how can you be sure it was Benny
怎么能确定是本尼干的
if you didn't actually see him do it?
因为我看到本尼拐上那条小路
B-b-because I saw Benny turn up the path,
两秒钟之后
and then two seconds later,
我就被一具喉咙被撕开的尸体绊倒了
I trip over a body with its throat ripped.
有没有听说过奥卡姆剃刀
Look, man, you ever hear of Occam's Razor?
14世纪英国奥坎逻辑学家威廉提出的原理  即"如无必要  勿增实体"
"简单的才是真相"  没那么复杂
"Keep it simple, stupid?" it's not that complicated.
这中间有很多漏洞  马丁
There's a lot of holes, Martin.
漏洞  我们现在要关注的
Holes?! The only holes we should be looking at
是被害者脖子上的洞
are in the vic's neck.
这像你认识的本尼会做的事吗
This sound like the Benny you know?
我不认得本尼
I don't know Benny.
你认识本尼
The Benny you know?
说什么呢
Say what?
我为什么有一种
Why am I getting the distinct impression
你哥哥在担保一个吸血鬼清白的感觉
that your brother is vouching for a vampire?
伙计们  不要吵
Guys, let's not argue.
没人在吵  但是如果是本尼
Nobody's arguing, but if this is Benny --
现在只是假设
and that's a big "If" --
就是他
Oh, it's him.
我跟他有交情  知道吗
I got history with the guy, okay?
我不会问都不问就下手的
I'm not signing up for a witch hunt.
我欠他的情不止这些
I owe him more than that.
全能的上帝啊
What in God's great creation
温彻斯特家的人怎么会欠吸血鬼的情
could a Winchester possibly owe a vampire?
我没有听错吧
Am I hearing this right?
听着  查明真相之前
Look, until we get the facts,
我们先收起嗜血冲动  把这件事做好
we stow the bloodlust and we work this case right,
不然我们分开行动
or we work it separately.
让他脑袋搬家才是把事做好
Doing it right would be separating his head from his shoulders.
我需要时间  萨姆
I just need some time, Sammy.
是吗  让尖牙鬼继续杀人  我看不行
Oh, yeah. Let the fang take another life? I don't think so.
你需要多久
How much time do you need?
你不是真的要听他的吧
You're not actually considering this?
几小时足够了
Couple hours, tops.
如果真的是本尼呢
And what if it turns out to be Benny?
如果真是本尼  我自己处理
Then it's Benny, and I'll deal with it!
几小时  迪恩  不能再多了
Couple hours, Dean. No more.
我回头联系你
I'll be in touch.
听我说
H-hey. Oh, look.
你开玩笑的吧
You're joking, right?
他一走我们就行动
We're doing this as soon as he pulls away.
不  不行  马丁
No, we're not, Martin.
我们得给他一点时间
We're gonna give him a little bit of time.
你的哥哥  你说了算
Hey, it's your brother. It's your call.
你还打算让他这样下去多久
How long are you gonna let him go on like this?
真相就摆在他面前
It's staring him right in the face.
有时候要看清真相很不容易
Well, sometimes it's not easy to see things for what they are.
德克萨斯州  克米特
捡球
Get the ball.
过来
Come here!
Come here.
好样的
Good job.
想好见他要说什么了吗
Thought about what you're gonna say to him?
我想了又想  想来想去
I've thought about it and thought about it,
但我还是不知道
and I still don't know.
肯定有很多人告诉你正确的事情是
Look, I'm sure you have a lot of people telling you
在这里的一切
what the right thing to do is here.
萨姆
Sam...
他是你的丈夫  艾米利亚
He's your husband, Amelia.
但是我不想
But I-I don't...
我不想去做正确的事
I don't want to do the right thing.
我是说你和我在一起就是正确的事情
I mean, this is the right thing, you and me.
也许我会因为说这句话而下地狱
And maybe I'm going to hell for saying this,
但是我不想就此放弃
but I'm not ready to give this up.
我也不想
Neither am I.
你介意我花几天时间清醒一下头脑吗
Would it bother you if I just took a few days to clear my head?
当然可以
Of course.
多长时间都行
Uh, take whatever time you need.
实际上  我已经想好要什么了
Actually, I already know what I want.
我猜猜  秋葵汤饭
Let me guess...gumbo?
在我看到那些派之前是这么想的
Was gonna be the gumbo till I saw pie.
特色山核桃派
Well, the special's pecan.
当然是了
Course it is.
我就要那个
Let's do that.
坏消息
Bad news.
你们的山核桃派卖完了  我命该如此
You're out of pecan. Story of my life.
没事的  也许你可以补偿给我
Uh, that's all right. Maybe you can make it up to me.
我事实上是来找一位老朋友的
I'm actually looking for an old friend of mine.
我听说他就在这附近  罗伊
I heard he's kicking around these parts. His name's Roy.
罗伊在这里上夜班
Well, Roy works the night shift here.
如果我们说的是同一个罗伊的话
I mean, if we're talking about the same Roy.
他住在一个破旧的帐篷里
Uh, yeah, he, uh, putts around in a beat-up camper.
看起来就像是恶魔禁地一样
Thing looks like a rolling deathtrap.
我还以为只有我
Yeah, I thought I was the only one
嘲笑他住的那一堆垃圾呢
who gave him trouble over that piece of junk.
那你知不知道
You wouldn't happen to know
他这几天把帐篷搭在哪
where he's parking that thing these days, would you?
他本来就把帐篷搭在后面
Well, he, uh, was parking it out back,
但他刚打电话告诉我
but just called to tell me
说他要从公路去磨坊河几天
he's gone up the road to Mill Creek for a few days.
好吧
Okay.
他说为什么了吗
Uh, did he say why?
我想是去钓鱼
Oh... fishing, I think.
他真的该休息一段了
He really deserves a break.
他近两周天天上双倍的班
He's been working doubles for the last two weeks straight.
这样吧
Um, listen, I, uh, I tell you what.
如果他在我找到他之前过来了
If he pops up before I can find him,
请你帮个忙让他给我打个电话
you do me a favor and just have him give me a buzz.
或者
Or...
你也可以直接打我
Could just drop a dime yourself.
当然可以
Sure thing...
迪恩
Dean.
你叫
And, uh, you are...?
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
伊丽莎白  好的
Elizabeth. All right.
我改天来吃派
Take a rain check on that pie.
好的
Definitely.
古德瑞的法式餐厅
请在嘟一声后留言
Leave a message at the beep.
本尼  我在卡伦科找到了一具
Benny. I got a body here in Carencro
脖子上被咬了两个洞的尸体
with two holes in it.
我又刚得知你去钓鱼了
And I just found out you went fishing.
需要我告诉你这像发生了什么吗
Do I need to tell you what this looks like?
一条新留言
不是我干的  迪恩
It's not me, Dean.
你说的是哪个"我"
Now, which "me" are we talking about.
本尼  还是罗伊
Benny...or Roy?
我只是想融入这一带
I'm just trying to blend in.
融入
"Blend in"?
你刚把谁埋了
Who'd you plant, Benny?
二号遇害者
Victim number two.
如果你想问我为什么不接电话
If you're concerned about the missed calls,
原因是我不想把你牵扯进来
I didn't want to get you involved.
那么现在
Now...
先放一放那事  谈一谈怎样
Want to safety that thing, talk a little bit or what?
我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
是独居的吸血鬼干的
Rogue vamp.
前几天晚上来到餐厅
Came into the cafe a couple nights ago.
名叫德斯蒙德的年轻人
Youngster goes by the name of Desmond.
他想起了过去的好时光
He, uh, he remembers me from the good old days.
过去的好时光
The good old days?
我知道这很难相信
I know it's hard to believe,
但我不是一直都像现在这么可爱招人喜欢
But I haven't always been this cute and cuddly.
他来和我叙叙旧  迪恩
He's chasing a memory, Dean.
仅此而已
That's all.
他在组建新的巢穴
He's crewing up a new nest.
他希望我能带给他一点人气
He's hoping I can give him some cred.
我拒绝了他
I told him no.
好吧
All right.
说到这一切都还好
So far, so good.
直接说那血案是怎么回事
Let's get to the part about the blood.
他想让我回心转意
Didn't want to take no for an answer.
他想刺激我  丢下死尸
He's trying to roust me out,
直到我变回来的自己  加入他
leaving dead bodies in my wake till I sign up.
两天两具尸体
Two bodies in two days.
没有人能把我赶出故乡  迪恩
No amateur is gonna kick me out of my hometown, Dean.
这次不行
Not this time.
"故乡"
"Hometown"?
你在这长大
You grew up here?
土生土长
Born and bred.
安德莉亚死后  你重出江湖
With Andrea gone and you hunting again,
似乎是时候到我回归故里了
seemed like the right time for a homecoming,
只有你们兄弟才能让我服服帖帖
you two being the only ones who keep all my ducks in a row.
我在一家餐厅重操旧业
Went back to my old job at the cafe...
我甚至找到一个我该负责的人
I even found someone I hold myself accountable to.
和我血肉相连的人  迪恩
Best kind of someone, Dean.
家人
Family.
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
我的曾孙女
My great-granddaughter.
真的吗
Really?
等等  你没有
Now, hold it, now. You didn't --
没有
Uh, no. No.
她知道吗
Does she know?
不知道
No.
不  对她而言  我不过是一个过客
No, as far as she's concerned, I was just another drifter.
我喜欢如此行事
I'd like to keep it that way.
在这里想过得舒服很艰难
It's been tough walking the line here
这些年在炼狱里
after all those years in purgatory
过惯了不缺食物的日子
not having to deal with the hunger.
但是伊丽莎白
But Elizabeth...
我让我变得诚实
She keeps me honest.
我终于觉得是时候处理这件事情
I finally feel like I got a handle on this thing.
处理事情
Handle on things?
本尼  你手上有两具死尸
Benny, you've got two stiffs on your hands
两个猎人对你穷追不舍
and two hunters on your ass.
拜托  是在餐厅找到我的笨蛋吗
Oh, please. The half-wit who found me at the cafe?
我倒想陪他玩玩
I'll take my chances with him.
那个笨蛋是我弟弟派来的  相信我
That half-wit was sent by my brother, and trust me --
我弟弟绝对不是你想去招惹的人
my brother's not someone you want to mess with.
我没时间陪他们玩  迪恩
I don't have time to worry about them, Dean.
我以前以为德斯蒙德不会惹祸上身
I didn't think Desmond had an ounce of steel in his spine,
但我错了
but I was wrong about that.
所以现在我要去做两天前就该做的事情
So now I'm gonna do what I should have done two days ago,
把他送到他该在的地方
which is put him back where he belongs.
你知道解决此事只有一个办法  对吗
You know there's only one way to do that, right?
就是让你袖手旁观
And that is for you to sit on the sideline
我会说服萨姆和马丁跟踪德斯蒙德
while I convince Sam and Martin to go after Desmond.
如果他们见到你
They see you out there,
他们不问青红皂白
they don't care if you're gonna be
会把你格杀勿论
collecting for the march of dimes.
你还没说话  他们就让你身首异处
They are gonna slice first and ask questions later.
你明白的
You know that.
你觉得他们会接手此事
You really think they'll go for that?
我来解释清楚
Let me get this straight.
我跟踪那小子
I follow your boy...
来到一条恐怖的小径
...down a freaking path
被惨遭吸血鬼杀害的尸体绊倒
and trip over fresh vamp kill,
而且你还亲眼所见
and then you practically catch him in the act
他在掩埋另外一具尸体
of burying a second body
你还要偏袒他吗
and you're still taking his side?
吸血鬼会找郊区落单的人下手
Vampires pick people off from the outskirts of town, okay?
不会舍近求远在他曾孙女
Not in the cafe that they work in
上班的餐厅下手
with their great-grandkids.
其实  杀害人类不是他的行事风格
In fact, killing any human -- it's not his style.
"不是他的行事风格"
"Not his style"?
迪恩  我们来此调查一具死尸
Listen, Dean, we came here on a dead body.
你让我们给你点时间
You asked for some time,
现在又发现一具尸体
and now there's another dead body.
我们还能相信你吗
Are we just going on trust here?
是的
Yes.
好吧
Okay.
因为死在我们手上的吸血鬼为数不少
Because we've killed for a lot less,
而且你知道他们对我们恨之入骨
and you know how these things turn out for us.
是的  我一清二楚
Yes, I do -- too well.
其实  我经历的每一段关系
In fact, every relationship I have ever had
在某种程度上都很糟糕
has gone to crap at some point.
但是我可以说唯独有本尼
But the one thing I can say about Benny --
他从没让我失望过
He has never let me down.
祝贺你  迪恩
Well, good on you, Dean.
经过这么多年你一定为终于找到
Must feel great finally finding someone you can trust
可以信任的人而高兴
after all these years.
我只想说本尼是无辜的
All I'm saying is that Benny is innocent.
不
No.
你感情用事
You're too close to this.
你不会找到他
You're not gonna find him.
如果你执意要做  我告诉你
And if you do, I'm gonna tell you this.
能捡回性命算便宜你了
You'll be lucky to get out alive.
如果你和他一起去  你也死期不远了
And you -- you go with him, you're a dead man -- period.
想想那些无辜的生命  迪恩
These are innocent lives we're talking about, Dean.
你还会为本尼的一片之词冒险吗
And you're willing to risk that on Benny's word alone?
我当然会
Damn right I am.
这是干什么
What...was that?
迪恩做了选择
Dean made his choice.
我们去忙正经事吧
Let's go do our job.
幸好你爸刚才没听到那些
Glad your dad wasn't around to hear that.
他会想把你们俩
He'd have a mind
从柴棚里揪出来  告诉你们那是什么
to take you both out the woodshed and show you what's what.
我也想亲自这么做
Half inclined to do it myself.
你给我听着
You listen to me.
我能带你来
I brought you into this.
也能轻松地把你丢出去
I can bring you out just as easy.
所以你想做的唯一一件事
So the only thing you're gonna be inclined to do
就是闭好嘴跟着我
is shut up and follow my lead.
好吧  你说了算
Okay. You say so.
我说  哥哥选择相信吸血鬼而不是弟弟
Just saying-- brother chooses a vampire over a brother?
我知道我会是什么感受
I know how I'd feel.
你是萨姆  对吧
You are Sam, right?
别紧张
Relax.
我不是来这打架的
I ain't here to fight.
我听说了发生在你身上的事
I heard about what happened to you.
真不公平
Rough deal.
是啊
Hmm.
谢谢你这么说
Yeah, well, I appreciate that.
现在我们陷入难题了  不是吗
We got ourselves a situation here now, though, don't we?
我想是的
Guess we do.
事实是我不能为此责怪你俩
Truth is, I can't blame either of you for what happened.
之前我觉得自己死定了
Hell, there were days there I thought I was a dead man.
但是当我回来的时候  我回来却面对这一切
But when I do come back and what I come back to is this,
我有时会想这是怎么回事
well, it ain't no great mystery if part of me is thinking,
现在这样到底是怎么了
"What's wrong with this picture?"
唐
Don--
萨姆  听我说完
Sam, let me finish.
我知道她还爱我
I know part of her loves me.
现在
And now...
她也爱你
part of her loves you.
但是只有艾米利亚自己知道对她来说
But the only one that knows what's best for Amelia
最好的选择是什么
is Amelia.
所以当一切说清楚
So when all of this is said and done
她也做出决定时
and she's made her decision,
我会尊重她的决定
I'll respect it.
如果你真的爱她  你也会这样做
And if you truly love her, you'll do the same.
再给他一杯
He could use another.
拜托
Come on.
他们说什么了
What'd they say?
他们不信  他们去找你了
They didn't go for it. They're on their way to you.
我也过去
I'd get scarce.
无意冒犯  迪恩  可你弟弟
No offense, Dean, but your little brother
可真是吓不了我
doesn't exactly put chills up my spine.
本尼  听我说
Benny, listen to me.
别低估我弟弟  好吗
Do not underestimate my little brother, okay?
有机会的话  他完全可以杀掉你
He can and will kill you given the chance.
好吧
All right.
那现在怎么办
So, what now?
我去找德斯蒙德
I go find Desmond.
带上我
You take me with.
我刚告诉你
Hey, I just told you --
你最好低调一点
best thing you can do is lay low.
这回不行  兄弟
That ain't gonna work this time, bub.
你带上我  否则我不告诉你他在哪
You take me with, or I don't tell you where he is.
你知道他在哪里吗
You know where he is?
他说除非我加入他的小巢
He said he's not gonna stop the killing
否则他不会停止杀戮
till I join his little nest.
死两个人已经够了
Two bodies is enough.
我跟他说我加入
I told him I'm in.
本尼
Benny.
迪恩  这是我的事
Dean, this is my fight.
你加不加入
Are you in or are you out?
什么东西把他吓跑了
Something spooked him.
艾米利亚・理查森
萨姆  我需要你的帮助  快来
萨姆
Sam.
Sam!
萨姆
Sam!!
真是温彻斯特家的人
Winchesters.
烦人
Man!
就是这里吗
This the place, huh?
计划是什么
So, what's the plan?
我先按兵不动  等你们去
I hang back while you guys
喝喝酒确认是否可以相互信任吗
do some trust falls and binge-drinking?
伙计  要不是我了解你
Man, if I didn't know you better,
我会说你还真是瞧不起吸血鬼啊
I'd say you have an extremely low opinion of us vamps.
这叫有益的怀疑精神
Call it healthy skepticism.
本尼可没告诉我他带了朋友过来
Benny never told me he was bringing a friend.
你不会废话太多吧
You're not gonna talk a lot, are you?
我这一整天
I've been dealing with crazy...
都跟神经病打交道
...all day.
混蛋
Son of a...
你可真是慢啊
It took you long enough.
差一点啊  伙计
You've lost a step, friend.
你不能再吃那些垃圾食品了
You need to lay off the junk food.
你还好吗
You okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
我在这里的生活结束了  对吧
My life here is over, isn't it?
恐怕是的
Afraid so.
一旦消息走漏出去
Once word gets out...
那些猎人就会追杀你
...the machete swingers that'll come for you...
你是对付不完的
You can't take them all.
那不可能
It's impossible.
就算你可以
And even if you could...
我们也会有问题
We'd have a problem.
我们这样的人  没法定居
Guys like us, we don't get a home.
也没有家人
We don't get family.
你有萨姆
You got Sam.
对
Yeah.
本尼  你必须躲起来
Benny, you got to go deep underground,
躲到没人知道你身份的地方
where nobody knows who you are.
是
Yeah.
我还有最后一件事情要做
I got one last thing I got to do.
呼叫艾米利亚・理查德森
您拨打的电话暂时无法接通
The person you are trying to reach is unavailable.
做什么呢
What are you doing?
我
I'm, uh...
我准备走了
I'm leaving.
什么
What?
唐在酒吧找到你了
Don found you at the bar.
艾米利亚
Amelia --
他威胁你
He threatened you.
艾米利亚  他没有威胁我
Amelia, no. He didn't threaten me.
听着  我只是想做正确的事情
Look, I'm just trying to do the right thing here.
"正确的事"
"The right thing"?
今早我们俩在一起就是正确的事情  忘了吗
This morning, you and I were the right thing, remember?
我很明白  你和唐需要一次机会
I know that you and Don deserve a chance, okay?
你心里也清楚
And...I think you know that, too.
给他一次机会吧  你不是也给了我吗
Just give him a chance -- like you gave me.
我是说
I mean...
艾米利亚  你拯救了我
Amelia, you saved me.
克米特26号公路
该走了  老兄
Time to go, buddy.
多谢你没有放弃我  老弟
Thanks for not giving up on me, brother.
别给我这样的机会
Don't give me a reason to.
嗨  迪恩
Hey, Dean.
我打电话就是要告诉你
Look, I'm just calling to let you know
问题已经解决了
that the situation is resolved.
本尼没说谎
Benny was not lying.
还有一个吸血鬼  我们一起解决了他
There was another vamp, and we ganked him -- together.
很好  迪恩
Oh. That's good, Dean.
闭嘴  听我说
Yeah, shut up and listen to me.
本尼远走高飞了  再也不会回来了
Benny's long gone, and he won't be coming back ever.
为了你好  别再找他了
So for your own sake, do not follow him.
明白了吗
Are we clear?
你用不着担心我  迪恩
You don't have to worry about me, Dean.
我也远走高飞了
I'm long gone, too.
马丁
Oh, and, Martin?
说
Yeah?
换个行当吧
Find a new line of work.
伊丽莎白来电
嘿  莉兹
Hey, Liz.
代班情况怎么样
How's your shift going?
说真的  她代替你干得不错
I'd say she's covering for you just fine...
本尼
Benny.
不过我们这些常客  还是想你
But us regulars -- we miss you.
你是谁
Who is this?
你应该知道我是谁
I think you know who this is.
你是怎么拿到她手机的
How the hell you get her phone?
喜欢吃樱桃酱吗
You enjoy the cherry?
别动
No!
抱歉
Sorry.
还没吃完呢
Not quite done yet.
联系上你的朋友了吗
Did you, uh, reach your friend okay?
是的  多谢
I did. Thanks.
不敢相信  我居然把手机掉在巴士上了
I can't believe I left my cell on the bus.
老婆常说我的脑袋要是没拧紧  肯定弄丢了
Wife says I'd lose my own head if it wasn't screwed on.
我还要再说一会儿
I'll just be another minute.
别着急
Well, you take your time.
谢谢
Thank you.
她是个好女孩
She's a nice girl.
对陌生人很友好
Takes kindly to strangers.
你立刻离她远点
You leave her alone -- now.
你距离多远
How far away are you?
一小时路程
An hour.
给你四十五分钟
You got 45 minutes.
小姐
Miss?
你的手机
Your cellphone.
胳膊别乱动  邪恶的东西
Lay down your arms, you unholy thing!
我现在来了
You got me here, now.
不如放了她  让她走
Why don't you just let her go and walk away?
我没这打算
I don't think so.
搞清楚  我可不是求你
You realize I'm not asking.
我非常清楚
I realize that completely.
罗伊  这是怎么回事
Roy, what's going on?
没事  莉兹
It's okay, Lizzie.
他不会伤害你
He ain't gonna hurt you.
难道不对吗
Ain't that right?
得了 说吧
Come on, now.
你我之前毫无过节
I got no beef with you. You got no beef with me.
我跟你这种人可有仇了
I got plenty of beef with your kind.
好吧
All right.
也许没错
That may be so,
但是和这里发生的事无关
but not for anything that happened here.
我没杀那些人
I did not kill those people.
我听说了
I heard.
你和迪恩在炼狱有过交情
You and Dean had a little purgatory reunion.
真感人
Touching.
罗伊
Roy...
就告诉我到底出了什么事吧
Please just tell me what's going on here.
拜托
Please.
我求你  别这么做
I'm asking you -- do not do this.
那个恶棍已经痛改前非了  好吗
The bad guy is gone, okay?
她不知道
She doesn't know...
本尼
Benny.
罗伊
Roy?
本尼是谁
Who's Benny?
"本尼是谁"
"Who's Benny"?
我们就弄个真相大白吧  如何
Let's find out, shall we?
别过来
Stay back!
看看
Look.
看见了吗
See that?!
瞳孔扩大
Dilated pupils!
头发直竖
Hair standing!
饥饿的征兆
Signs of hunger!
别担心
Don't worry.
他不会吃掉自己的亲骨肉的
He won't feed off his own flesh and blood.
"亲骨肉"
"Flesh and blood"?
告诉她啊  本尼
Tell her, Benny.
告诉她你就是她失散多年的爷爷
Tell her how you're her long-lost grandpappy.
告诉她你欠下了多少条人命
Tell her about all the dead you left behind.
告诉她你是个什么怪物
Tell her about the monster that you are!
你想怎么样
What do you want?
还不够清楚吗
Isn't it obvious?
我想要你的脑袋
I want your head on a stake.
罗伊  不要
Roy, no.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
希望他们给你在炼狱
Well, hope they're saving a special place for you...
留了个好地方
wherever it is you come from.
不要
No!!
我觉得今晚还不错
I feel all right tonight.
喂
Yeah?
迪恩
Dean?
等一下
H-hang on.
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth?
你说要是我看到他  就打给你的
Y-you told me to call you if I saw...him.
你的意思是  看到罗伊了
What do you mean? Roy?
他
Is --
他现在就在你旁边
Is he there right now?
伊丽莎白  出什么事了
Elizabeth, what's going on?
快来吧
Just come.
艾米利亚・理查森
萨姆  我需要你的帮助  快来
小萨姆
Sammy?
"萨姆  我需要你的帮助  快来"
"Sam, I need your help. Come quick."
这招不错
Nice one.
用个火炉就换来了艾米利亚的电话
Swapping Amelia's phone out with a burner,
发了求救短信
Sending a distress signal...
你找准了我的死穴
You got me good.
你什么时候干的
When did you do that?
有一阵了  以备我不时之需
While back, in case I needed it.
看来我的决定是对的
Looks like I made the right call.
你看见她了吗
So, did you see her?
是的  我看见她了
Yeah. Yeah, I saw her.
她挺好的  不过这你也知道
And she's doing just fine. But, 'course, you know that.
其实我并不知道
Actually, I didn't.
我只知道这是唯一让你休息的办法
I did know it was the only way to get you to lay off.
然后呢
So?
成了吗
Is it done?
没错  成了
Yeah, it's done.
有人伤亡吗
Any casualties?
马丁死了
Martin.
是本尼吗
Was it Benny?
他自找的  萨姆
He had it coming, Sam.
我告诉你发生什么事了吧
I'll tell you what happened.
我知道是怎么回事  迪恩
I-I know what happened, Dean.
你还想不想听我说了
Okay, you want to listen to me or not?
见鬼
Damn it.
我知道是你
I knew that was you.